(Howard:)We're not really gonna go
to the North Pole with him, are we?
SHELDON:
I'm still within earshot.
You may wanna wait
for my door to close.
[DOOR CLOSES]
(Howard:)We're not really gonna go
to the North Pole with him, are we?
(Leonard:)Hang on, let's talk about it. This is a
National Science Foundation expedition.
(Leonard:)I don't know
how we can turn it down.
Easy. Instead of saying, "No, we don't
wanna go on an NSF expedition," say:
"No, we don't wanna spend three months
stuck in a cabin in the Arctic Circle...
...with an anal nutbag."
(Raj:)But if we were part of the team
that confirmed string theory...
(Raj:)...we could drink for free in any bar,
in any college town...
(Raj:)...with a university
that has a strong science program.
(Leonard:)Howard, this is big science.
You could be the engineer...
(Leonard:)...who builds the equipment
that puts us on the cover of magazines.
(Howard:)I could also be the engineer who builds
the crossbow that kills Sheldon.